I'm traveling with Leo! Yay!
I'm going to take a bath!
Oh, my gosh.
Here you go, pack.
Ta-da!
Eels.
Eels and eggs?
I'm back in the bath.
Good night.
Hello, everyone.
Hello, Leo.
Today...
My birthday is coming up soon.
I'm traveling with Leo.
Yay!
Thanks for the long trip, Leo!
It was a very long trip.
We got on the highway and worked hard!
I'm hungry for a while longer.
I think I'm going to go out to eat!
I heard there is a restaurant like Miyake's.
I heard there is a restaurant where Leo can eat.
I'm going to go there for now!
Stato
Haircon
The restaurant is crowded right now, so I'm waiting with Leo-kun
The terrace seats are for dogs only, and the dogs are normal and exclusive.
It's hot! Too hot!
So cute, guys.
Leo.
So cute.
Rick mistook me for a baby earlier today, too.
It's so hot.It's so hot!
Ta-da! The rice has arrived!
Delicious, a bowl of rice topped with leeks, tuna and
and miso soup with blue fish!
Leo is doing well!
Let's get started...
Leo, no!
Can't you sit down?
Yes!
Laver Erie!
Bon appétit.
I'll eat it with my mouth.
Yum!
Too good!
Shizuoka is all about seafood!
We passed by Atami today!
The rice is delicious!
Nugitro, my favorite!
I can't eat well!
Bon appétit!
Delicious.
Neck, I'll have some too.
Neck!
The waiter said I could sit on the chair.
Yes, ma'am.
I'll see you later.
See you later.
Great!
It's so nice to have an illuminated enemy dog only, isn't it?
Horse.
You didn't eat your food.You didn't eat your food.
Well, I'm going to finish my food.
See you later.
All done! Thank you for the food!
Thank you for the food! You've been a good boy!
A couple, a man and a woman, who were eating in the restaurant? who was eating in the restaurant talked to me.
They are so cute! They said, "Your dog and I are both cute! He said, "Your dog and I are cute!
We became good friends.
He said he knows what I like, so he is going to promote me from now on.
So many kind people!
Well then, let's go to the next destination! Bye bye!
Ta-da! Here comes the dog station!
Is this it? Aiken no Eki?
That's awesome!
I want to go in there!
Wow, what's a dog bus?
Look, what is it? Look at this.
What is that?
Oh, my God.
There's a puppy.
He's on it.
I don't know what it is.
Am I allowed to get on it? I'm not sure what it is.
That's amazing!
It's amazing that there's a place like this.
I didn't know there was a place for dogs.
Let's go in.
I was just shopping.
I bought a Ryok pillow and some snacks.
Look at this!
I heard you can make it.
I want to make one!
I'll ask the shopkeeper.
Here.With this.
I did this.
Here.
They're going to put it in.
Stroke of touch on the screen.
Let's read it in.
Finished.
Oh, done.
Then, insert it all the way to the back.
Finished.
What shall we do?
He's going to choose.
Shall I choose a minion?
Wow!
Wow, it's done.
He's so cute.
Just the part I want to show you.
I can see.
It's done.
All right, let's go, Mr. Walking.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
We got a lot of stuff.
So cute!
This is great!
I can't see it... probably because of reflections.
I wanted to get the middle one, but it ended up on the edge.
Maybe there was a setting or something.
Well, I'm going to go to the hotel now.
I guess I'm tired. I'm going to the hotel anyway.
Let's go!
Ta-da!
Here we are!
It's a very mountainous road, Leo.
Scary.Scary.
Oh! It's so big!
Wow! This must be a hotel where you can stay with your dog!
It's so neat!
It has a terrace!
Yes! It's got an outdoor hot tub!
No, wait! What if there are bugs!
Neo!
Neo! Neo!
He, uh... he hates me.
I think he's here to show me some money.
It looks like they have a lot of stuff for dogs, too.
And a bed.
Well, I guess I'll go with Leo.
There we go.
Oh, it's indirect lighting.
Oh, I feel lighter.
That's great, Rick.
You look like you're having fun.
Oh, my God.
Bath.
Nami, I'm gonna go wash my hands.
Neo, why don't you stay here while I get in?
Wow, it's so beautiful.
Nice, Neo. You look beautiful.
Where are you going? Neo.
Neo, where are you going?
Neo, you're staying here today.
That's so sweet.
What are we going to do, stay the night?
I'd like to do a little bit of everything, a little bit of everything, to get Leo ready for this set.
Here we go.
Okay, so...Yes, I mean.
I'm going to Dockla now.
I'm going for a walk.
And then
I go for a walk
Dinner?
Some kind of eel?
I bought some delicious eels.
And then...
There was a cake shop that looked good.
It was cheap to begin with.
It looked like they were open in the evening.
So...
I got it at half price.
I bought it very cheaply!
I'm going to make Leo's
I've brought some food for Leo
I brought some food for Leo.
I'd like to give it to him.
Here you go.
Here's your dinner.
Dinner! Dinner!
Your plate is different from usual
Dinner.
No, it's not.
Do you want some food?
I won't give it to you. Please eat by yourself.
You eat by yourself? You haven't been eating by yourself lately, have you?
Eat it.
No, I can't.
Oh, no!
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Want to try some of this?Want to try some of this?
Like furikake.
Bonito puffs.
Shall we put it on?
Yes, sir.
I wonder if she's just eating the sprinkles or if she's eating the rice as well.
Is it good?
I'm so happy for you!
I'm... oh, it's cold.
I'm going to take a bath now.
Looking forward to it
I think the sun's gonna go down in a little bit.
It's about 7:00 now.
I'm going to go in
I'm eating.
Great.
Okay, I'll get ready for the bath.
Yay.
He's coming in for a bath.
Neo.
Neo...
Let's relax on the terrace.
Let's get out.
Oh, here he comes.
Wow!
Feels good.
There's no bugs.
What's wrong?
I don't know. Maybe it's early.
It's red.
It's beautiful.
Come here.
Come here.Come here.
He's so cute.
Come on!
Yes!
Come on! Yeah! Yeah! Come on!
Come on! Kun!
It's so good, isn't it?
It's so good.
Well, well, well. Back?
Oh, my gosh, back?
Is he back?
Good night, sweetheart.
Good night.
We'll be plating the next video!
Extra
Delicious, these ramen noodles.
Good night.
Is it good?
Isn't it great? I can't believe it's actually a petting zoo.
I mean, I mean, this... I mean, the scum bath, you know?
It's like a regular bathtub in a Japanese inn.
That's amazing.
I'm peeking.
He's a boy now.
I kissed him.
Out?
It's dark in here.
Hito-chan, let's get out of here.
It's about time.It's about time.
I'm gonna miss you.
I gotta go. Bye.
Oh, and, by the way...
You're standing on your feet a little bit.
That's cute.
He's cute.
There we go.
I got a banana today.
What's up?
It's millefucka today.
Feels good.
I didn't want to pack a lot of skincare, so I've been saving it for first.
I'm supposed to put on three or something for sunset.
I'm sorry, sorry, sorry.
Sorry, sorry, sorry.
There's some kind of pimple here.
Something like an allergy maybe.
I'm going to bed.
What's wrong?
There's still some food left.
Juttib.
Thank you for watching.
Good night. - Good night.
Good night.
Good night, sir.
I like the hair dryer a little bit,
I often blow dryer on my ears.
Hair dryer done!
It's so smooth!I'm sooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooo!
All right, let's go have dinner.
Hey, come here.
Hey, you, come here.
Come here.
It's totally dark.
Oh, before you go...
Last year.
Yeah, I bought something.
I didn't buy myself anything.
But here's what I bought today.
It's not for me.
For Leo.
This is...
I got it at ITMX.
First, the one I showed you today.
This one.
This is for Leo.
Neo.
It's in here.
You can't see it because of the reflection.
Isn't it amazing? Look at this.
I don't know how to open this.
I think I'm gonna break something.
Ha!
It didn't break.
Isn't this amazing?
It's so cute!
I'm gonna put it on a collar.
With your name on it.
I thought you said December 28.
It only has December on it.I'm only in December.
You're like a 12-year-old dog.
That's funny.
I should've checked.
First of all...
That's right.
Ta-da!
This is Leo's pillow.
A pillow for Leo's chin!
Isn't he cute?
Isn't this cute?
Leo, this one.
This is Leo's pillow.
This is Pui's pillow.
Sit down.
Sit.
That's normal.
Oh.
Sit.
You just used that.
I pointed a camera at you and you didn't use it.
I don't like the camera.
You don't like it.
It's cold.
Sol Frappéro.
It's a cute little bedtime pillow.
Cute bed pellows inspired by sea animals.
Crunchy.
Cold
Amazing.
Yes, eat it.
And next.And on and on.
Maybe.
This is the best part, isn't it?
Ta-da!
Sweets!
Like Leo's sweet potato chips.
I'm going to give them to him
I'm going to give it to him when I'm eating.
You did it!
It's a snack!
It's so cute!
So cute!
I don't know what I'm gonna do.
Sweets.
My Kinmedai rice crackers!
Shizuoka Matcha Langdosha
Okocha Langdosha!
And, I'm going to eat!
Okay, I'm going to eat dinner now!
I'm so hungry!
I'm going to eat eel!
Yay! Bye bye!
Ta-da!
Eel.
Eel and egg?
That's not an amen.
Looks so good!
She's so shaggy and clean.
It's terrible that she smokes like this.
I think so too.
Bon appétit!
Looks super delicious!
It's luxurious, isn't it?It's a luxury, isn't it?
Thanks for the food.
See you in the next video.
Bon appétit!
Mmm!
Soft and fluffy.
Soft and fluffy!
I knew it was good.
I love it!
Mmmmmm!
The eggs look so delicious!
Mmm!
Yum! Yum!
I can't get enough of this!
Sweet!
I love sweet eggs.
And you're so cute, Mario.
But I'm gonna eat this.
Hey.
Neck, you want some of these?
Is it big?
It's my first time.
Come on, man.
There we go.
What's that?
Hey, hey, hey.
Good night.
Just a little rub.
I see the dog in the next room is moving.
You don't want it?
No.I don't want it
I don't want it.
How can I not want it?
Is it hard?
It's super tasty.
I'm so happy.
Seafood for lunch was delicious.
And the eel at night is delicious!
It's so good!
Mmmmmm...
So many things!
Mmm.
Delicious.
Let's close the curtains. Let's close them in a circle.
Tasty?
Is it good?
He likes it.
I like this lunch box too.
It's delicious.
I've never had an egg omelet on an eel before.
It's so good!
Thank you for the food! It was so delicious!
Eel and egg is so good!
I'm so happy, I want to go to bed!
I can sleep now!
I'm so happy, but listen!
I bought some Cuys!
It's a birthday present. It's on YouTube.
Since I'm traveling with Leo.
I thought it would be nice to have something like that.
I just bought it.
Maybe I'll still eat it.I'll still eat it.
I'll take it.
Ta-da!
Look at this.
Mongulan!
A little melted.
It's just like in the old days.
I bought it at a retro cake shop.
I bought it.
It's a little bit like that
I don't have a fork.
Not at home.
I eat with chopsticks.
And that's it.
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh.
Bon appétit!
Happy birthday to you
Happy Birthday Dear Hit Girl
Happy Birthday to you
I'm so thankful for some kind of cake.
I see that you are often allowed to eat it even near your birthday.
I was wondering what you would like to eat the most and I felt like Mont Blanc!
Bon appétit!
I'll start with the chestnuts.
Looks delicious!
Ah~~n
Wow, this is delicious!
Wow, it's good.
I'm so happy.
Looks super delicious.
It's a chestnut.
What is this?I don't know what it is.
It's not too sweet.
Mmmmmm
Delicious!
Too good!
I can't get enough of this!
The end. Thank you for watching.
Delicious!
Too good!
It tastes like chestnuts.
What is it?
Lambraces? Rumplice?
It's so flavorful!
Crunchy.
Can we make momulan at home?
I'd like to make some.
Delicious!
I'm so happy!
Thank you very much for the food.
It was delicious!
Very tasty!
So cute!
Ryo usually doesn't play with toys.
But this is his only favorite toy.
So I brought it along.
Isn't it cute?
Does it flicker?
Do you think it might...
Check it out.
Neo.
He's so cute.
I don't like it.I don't like it.
It looks like it's going to stick to my hair.
Unlike me.
You know how they say they sleep with their owners?
That's about the extent of it, unlike me.
I don't think you're mocking me.
I feel like I'm calling myself a bruiser.
It's 9:00.
It's only 9:00.
The possibilities are endless.
Ayako is out of control.
The possibilities are always endless.
I'm not afraid.
With you.
Delicious eels.
Maybe I'll watch TV.
It's nighttime.
It's time to sleep.
Hey...
I just took another bath.
It felt so good.
I'm going to sleep now.
That was super fun.
It feels good to be outside.
See you tomorrow.
I'll take a bath in the morning.
I'm staying over for my birthday today.
I guess you could say that.
Birthday?
Birthday sleepover for a birthday.
I don't know.
I don't know. It's not like there's nothing going on.
I wrote him a letter saying...I wrote him a letter saying.
I can't believe I'm reading a letter I never saw.
I used to read them at my birthday party.
But I don't get that chance anymore.
I thought I'd like to write you a letter.
I think I'd like to write to you.
I wrote about what I'm becoming to you and to me.
Please listen to it.
I'll read it.
Thank you very much.
To the advertising culture
Hitaka Sakare turns 22
I've turned one more year older
I'm both sad and happy
For those of you who recently fell in love with me
You may not be able to imagine...
I've been a member of the Special Selection since I was in eighth grade.
I've been working as a special selector
Now I'm all dressed up and I'm wearing
I'm wearing clothes between my backs.
But in the beginning, I didn't aim at anything
I was just a 14 year old kid doing the best I could with what I had
I was a 14 year old kid.
I am here today because of the people who found me back then and the people who have supported me to this day.
I am filled with gratitude to all the people I have met.
I am grateful for the many people who often tell me how great I am, how much they respect me, and how much they admire me.
But I'm not great at all. I'm doing my best because everyone is giving me the stick.
I am also an idol, but at 22 years old, I am still a child who is trying to grow up and become an adult.
I sometimes hit bumps, I sometimes worry, and I sometimes feel like I'm going to give up.
But I am able to do my best because everyone supports me and smiles a lot when I perform live on stage.
I am able to be the kind of person I like to be.
I want to be a person who can do my best for everyone.
In elementary and junior high school, I was saved a lot by TV.
When I was in elementary school, I was afraid that if I said something like this, people would hate me,When I was in elementary school, I was afraid that if I said something like this, people would hate me,
I was afraid that if I said I wanted to be an idol, I would be made fun of.
My pleasure was watching TV.
I want to be like Kirei, who gave me such pleasure back then.
I will continue to do my best so that everyone can love this moment that we are living in.
I still make mistakes from time to time, but I will always give it my all.
Thank you for liking me like this.
Thank you for loving me as my mother.
I will continue to do my best.
From Kazuo Sakai
Letter
I'm very embarrassed.
I wrote what I really think.
I'm sorry.
Well...
I really didn't know anything when I first started.
I didn't know how to sing or dance or anything.
Because there were always people who supported me in every stage of my life
I've been able to continue until now.
I don't have the screen that you're looking at now.
I think that I am able to meet
I think that I am able to meet everyone.
Every second, every minute, every hour, every day, I give it my all.
It's the only time, the only live at that time, the only live at that time, the only live at that time
I who am only at that time
I had people who supported me like that at all times
I really
I am very grateful and thankful.
I was given the position of the red center of the return trip,
I am also grateful for the fact that you have accepted me.
I wonder if there might be some people who wonder why they are left out.
I don't know, maybe there are some people who wonder why we leave one thing out.
I don't know.
But I am happy to be able to move.But I am happy to move.
Everyone thinks it's good for arsenic,
Because there are people who are thinking of me,
I will do my best to fulfill this role.
I thought it was something too big for a while.
But
I've been able to do this because people have been asking for it
I have made it this far.
I'm going to keep on doing it.
I'm going to continue to do it.
When you appear in something like that...
I'll say, "She's the center order.
She's a trait member.
I'm a member of characteristics.
I'm going to be recognized in various ways.
They're all very attractive.
I'm going to do my best.
Please continue to support me!
Well, let's go to bed.
I'm tired today.
I'm going to bed.
You've had a long day, haven't you?
Yeah.
We've been to a lot of places I don't know.
I think I'll go to bed.
Good night.
See you tomorrow.
I have work tomorrow.
I'm going home first thing in the morning.I'm leaving first thing in the morning.
Check out first thing in the morning.
I'm going straight home.
That's too bad.
I'll go to work and do my best.
Sorry, Riku.
Good night.